zyltec.com 2009-04-22

# ZylTec - Privacy

| 

(Last Updated: April, 2006)

At ZylTec, Inc. ("ZylTec," "we," or "us"), we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy (this "Policy") describes how personal information is collected from users of the ZylTec website at www.zyltec.com or other websites operated by us (each a "Site"), and how that information is used and disclosed. By using our Site, you consent to the terms of this Policy.

>What is Personal Information?

Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as an individual's name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other account number, and information about that individual’s activities when directly linked to him or her, such as information about his or her purchases. Personal information also includes demographic information, such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies an individual.

Personal information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of products, services or customers from which individual customer identities have been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Likewise, information about the products you purchase may be collected and combined with information about the products purchased by others. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new products and services, and tailor existing products and services to customer desires.

Personal Information We Collect

You provide personal information to us in a number of ways when you visit the Site. For example, you provide us with personal information when you: 

  1. register on the Site;
  2. participate in a survey, contest or sweepstakes on the Site;
  3. contact us by e-mail for any reason (such as to contact our Customer Service team or to provide us with your comments/feedback); or
  4. post personal information on any message boards or other interactive areas on the Site.

We collect your name, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address, telephone number and certain information about your company (e.g., number of employees, number of locations, etc.) in this manner. Additionally, when you contact us to request technical support, you may provide us with computer databases or other system information that may contain other personal information. If you provide us with such system information that contains personal information, we will treat the system information as "personal information" under this Policy. 

We also collect personal information from you if you submit a job application or résumé to us via e-mail. Personal information collected in this regard includes your name and e-mail address, as well as other employment related information that you provide to us in the résumé and/or application.

Additionally, when you visit our Site, some information is automatically collected, such as your computer's operating system and browser type, your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time and date of your visit. This information is collected through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer by a web site to give you a unique identification. We use cookies on our Site, among other things, to keep you logged in to the Site, to count the number of unique computers visiting the Site, to record your user preferences and to ensure that you do not see the same advertisements repeatedly. We treat automatically collected information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the personally identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only.

How We Use Personal Information

In general, we use personal information to provide you with product support, to otherwise respond to your requests and inquiries, to maintain a record of our dealings with you, to develop new products and services and to inform you about products or services we think will be of interest to you. For example, we use your information to provide you with product support, to send you promotional materials via e-mail and postal mail, to improve our products and services and to develop new products and services. When we use personal information in our internal marketing efforts, we provide you with choices (see "Choice," below). We may also receive information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, and may combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you. If we do so, this Policy governs such information.

Sharing of Personal Information

We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy. We may share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, for example, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, mailing items and fulfilling or delivering orders. In all cases we limit the information shared with our third-party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions. We are not responsible for any additional information you provide to these parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them.

We also disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our customers' rights, property or safety; to protect our customers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, our Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay. Unless we believe the law requires otherwise, we will attempt to contact you before disclosing your personal information to comply with legal process.

In addition, information about our customers, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets.

Analytics

We have contracted with Google AdWords, MSN adCenter, and Yahoo! Search Marketing to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting web traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs,' and/or other activities on our website. No personally identifiable data is collected by or transferred to them. Where authorized by us, they may use cookies, Web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors.

  * To learn more about Google AdWords, click on the following link: <http://adwords.google.com/>
  * To learn more about Microsoft adCenter, click on the following link: <http://advertising.msn.com/MSNadCenter/LearningCenter/adtracker.asp>
  * If you choose, you may opt out from Yahoo! Search Marketing's collection of such information outside of the Yahoo! network of websites, by clicking on the following link: <http://docs.yahoo.com/info/privacy/us/ysmt.html>

Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site may contain links to other Web sites. Links from our Site to other sites or content are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties or other sites. Any personal information you provide on linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

Use of our Site by Children

We encourage parents to take an active interest in their children's use of the Internet. The Site is not designed to collect information from children who are under 13 years of age, and we do not intend to collect such information. If you are under 13, you should not provide information on our Site.

Security

We have put into place reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and alteration of information while it is under our control. We cannot, however, guarantee protection of all information against interception, misappropriation, misuse or alteration, or that your information may be not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. Furthermore, we have no control over the security of other sites you might visit, interact with or do business with. Orders placed on our Site are protected by an encryption technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to ensure privacy and security when submitting an order.

When you register on the Site, we ask you to create a login name and password. To protect the confidentiality of your personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused or otherwise misappropriated.

Choice

To opt-out of receiving communications from us, or to make changes to your personal information maintained by us, we provide you with the following options: you may 

  1. follow the "Unsubscribe" instructions contained in the communication from us;
  2. e-mail our Customer Support team at [support@zyltec.com](mailto:support@zyltec.com); or
  3. write to us at the following address with your request:  
ZylTec, Inc.  
Customer Support  
4580 Klahanie Drive SE #402  
Issaquah, WA 98029-5812  
United States of America 

If, in the future, we decide to share personal information with any third parties for their own marketing purposes, we will update this Policy to reflect such change and provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of such disclosure of your personal information.

Policy Changes

We will modify this Policy if our privacy practices change in the future. We will notify you of such changes only by posting the modified Policy on our Site and indicating at the top of the Policy the date it was last updated. We encourage you to review this Policy each time you visit our Site to see if it has been updated since your last visit and to make sure you understand how information you provide will be used.

Your Comments or Concerns

We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this Policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you may reach us via e-mail at [support@zyltec.com](mailto:support@zyltec.com) or telephone at +1 (425) 836-5400.
